salvage: v.   救助，营救；打捞
Lesson 32. A lost ship. The salvage operation had been a complete failure. The small ship,
第32课。一艘丢失的船。打捞操作是完全失败的。小船，
Elcor, which had been searching the barren sea for weeks, was on its way home. A radio message
埃尔科（Elcor）正在搜寻贫瘠的大海数周，他正在回家。无线电消息
from the mainland had been received by the ship's captain instructing him to give.
该船的队长指示他给他付出。
sunken: adj. 沉没的
Up the search, the captain knew that another attempt would be made later. For the sunken ship
在搜索中，船长知道稍后将进行另一次尝试。对于沉没的船
cargo: n.   货物, bullion: n.   金条；银条, find: n.   找到的物品
he was trying to find had been carrying a precious cargo of gold bullion.
他试图发现载有一枚珍贵的金条货物。
scour: v.   彻底搜索
Despite the message, the captain of the Elcor decided to try once more. The sea bed was scoured
尽管有消息，但Elcor的队长决定再次尝试。海床被搜寻
item: n.   物件
with powerful nets and there was tremendous excitement on boardwenda. Chest was raised from the
有强大的网络，木板世界引起了极大的兴奋。胸部从
bottom, though the crew were at first under the impression that the lost ship had been found.
底部，尽管船员起初是在发现失落的船上的印象。
chest: n.   大箱子, contents: n.   （复数）所装的东西
The contents of the chest proved them wrong. What they had in fact found was a ship which had
胸部的内容证明了他们错了。他们实际上发现的是一艘船
chest: n.   大箱子, belongings: n.   （复数）所有物
been sunk many years before. The chest contained the personal belongings of a seaman.
被沉没了很多年。胸部包含一个海员的个人财产。
Allen Fielding. There were books. Clothing and photographs. Together with letters which the
艾伦·菲尔丁。有书。衣服和照片。以及字母
salvage: v.   救助，营救；打捞
seaman had once received from his wife. The captain of the Elcor ordered his men to salvage as
海员曾经从妻子那里收到。埃尔科（Elcor）的队长命令他的士兵抢救
item: n.   物件
much as possible from the wreck. Nothing of value was found. But the numerous items which were
从残骸中尽可能多。找不到价值。但是众多的项目
brought to the surface proved to be of great interest from a heavy gun that was raised.
事实证明，从一个重型枪中引起了人们的极大兴趣。
chest: n.   大箱子, cruiser: n.   巡洋舰
The captain realized that the ship must have been a cruiser. In another chest, which contained
船长意识到这艘船一定是巡洋舰。在另一个箱子里
belongings: n.   （复数）所有物
the belongings of a ship's officer. There was an unfinished letter which had been written on March 14th.
船员的财产。3月14日有一封未完成的信。
1,943. The captain learned from the letter that the name of the lost ship was the Karen.
1,943。船长从信中得知失落的船的名字是凯伦。
find: n.   找到的物品
The most valuable find of all was the ship's logbook, parts of which it was still possible to read.
最有价值的发现是该船的日志，其中仍有可能阅读。
piece: v.   拼成整体
From this the captain was able to piece together all the information that had come to light.
由此，船长能够将所有消息揭示的所有信息拼凑在一起。
convoy: n.   护航, submarine: n.   潜水艇
The Karen had been sailing in a convoy to Russia when she was torpedoed by an enemy submarine.
当凯伦（Karen）被敌方潜艇炸毁时，凯伦（Karen）一直在车队驶向俄罗斯。
naval: adj. 海军的
This was later confirmed by naval official at the Ministry of Defiance after the Elcor had returned.
埃尔科（Elcor）返回后，海军官员在反抗部的海军官员后来证实了这一点。
item: n.   物件
Home, all the items that were found were sent to the war museum.
家，所有发现的物品都被送到战争博物馆。